大家好，我是Francois
hi everyone I'm francois
hi everyone i'm francois
非常感谢组织者的受害者
thanks a lot to the victim of organizers
非常感谢维生素C的眼镜邀请我发言
thanks a lot to the vitcom for glasses for inviting me to speak
邀请我今天发言
for inviting me to speak today
今天，我将会谈论特权的问题
today so i'm going to be talking about privileges
所以我将会谈论特权的问题
so I'm going to be talking about privileges
这是我建立的一个工具，让你
which is a tool that i built that lets you
这是一个工具，我建立了
which is a tool that I built
让你
that lets you
直接在你的IDE中阻止你的组件
prevent your components instantly directly in your IDE
直接在你的IDE中防止你的组件
prevent your components instantly directly in your ide
这里有一个来自previewjs com的快速预览。
so here's a very quick preview from previewjs com
但我将会
but I'm going to be
但我还会再来看看
but i'm going to be coming back to it
回来的时候，有一个稍微详细的
coming back to it with a slightly more detailed
与一个稍微更详细的概述
with a slightly more detailed overview
概述
overview
首先，我将谈论我为什么要建立它
at first i'm going to talk about why i built it
首先，我要谈一谈我为什么要建立它
at first I'm going to talk about why I build it
以及它如何融入其中
and how it fits into it
以及它是如何融入其中的
以及它是如何使其成为可能的，首先
and how it makes it possible in the first place
以及它是如何在第一时间使之成为可能的
因此，让我们从创建一个反应式应用程序开始
so let's start by creating a react app
所以让我们从创建一个react应用开始
我以react为例
and i'm using react as an example
and I'm using react as an example
但它也能与视图和实体一起工作
but it also works with view and solid
但它也适用于视图和实体，所以yarn创建react应用
but it also works with view and solid so yarn create react app
所以yarn创建反应式应用程序
so yarn create react app
食物
food
安装软件包
installing packages
安装软件包 这可能需要几分钟的时间
installing packages this might take a couple of minutes
这可能需要几分钟的时间
this might take a couple of minutes
我没有几分钟的时间了，我要停止这一切。
i do not have a couple of minutes i'm gonna stop that
我没有几分钟的时间
I do not have a couple of minutes
我要停止这一切
I'm gonna stop that
而不是
and instead of
yarn我将使用pnpm
yarn i'm gonna use pnpm
我要用pnpm来代替yarn，这样会快一点
yarn I'm gonna use pnpm which is a little bit faster
这是一个小的速度
which is a little bit faster
它实际上是什么维生素现在使用
it's actually what vit uses nowadays
它实际上是维生素现在使用的东西
而不是
and instead of
创建机架式应用，我会使用创建维生素，因为
create racked app i'm gonna be using create vit because well
创建反应应用程序，我会使用创建维生素，因为
create react app I'm gonna be using creat vit because
因为这是Vitcom，所以
well this is vitcom right so
这就是vitcom，对吗？
this is vitcom right so
为什么不在PNPM上创建Vit
why not pnpm create vit
为什么不采用PNP创建Vit
这是什么，这是超级快的我的签证应用程序
and this is what this is super fast my visa app
这就是我的视频应用，这就是超级快的视频应用。
and this is what this is super fast my video app
完善的反应脚本
react abscript perfect
我的视频应用
react appscript perfect
pmpm store
pmpm安装
pmpm install
嗯呢
和
and
我们做得很好
we're done cool
我们已经完成了
所以现在
so now
所以，现在我们有了这个美丽的代码库，已经
so now we have this beautiful code base that has been
我们有这个美丽的代码库，一直在自动
we have this beautiful code base that has been automatically
自动排出的
automatically draining
为我们生成的
draining generated for us
generated for us
而它的代码是美丽的
and it's the code is beautiful
它的代码是美丽的，它的代码是美丽的
但实际的应用程序也很美
but the actual app is beautiful as well
所以让我们进去运行它
so let's go in run it
所以，让我们去运行它，让我们去piang piang。
so let's go in run it let's go piang piang
让我们开始吧！让我们开始吧！让我们开始吧！让我们开始吧！让我们开始吧！让我们开始吧！
let's go pm pm dev
设计
dev
让我们打开这个
let's open this
它是美丽的
and it is beautiful
它是美丽的，看看这一切
and it is beautiful look at all this
看看这一切美丽的白色空间
look at all this beautiful white space
美丽的白色空间
beautiful white space
更重要的是，看看视频标志上的悬停效果
more importantly look at the hover effects on the vid logo
更重要的是
more importantly
看看视频标志上的封面效果
look at the cover effects on the vid logo
这就是
that are
以及
that are as well as
as well as
反应的标志，但维生素的标志是更花哨的
the react logo but the vit logo is even more fancy
我认为有人花了很多时间来调整这个
i think someone spent a lot of time tweaking this
I think someone spent a lot of time tweaking this
并使它只是
and making it just
完美的火花，无论如何
perfectly sparkly anyway
完美的火花
perfectly sparkly
总之，所以
anyway so
所以我们有这个计数器，这不是用来演示的。
so we have this counter and this is this is not for demo
我们有这个计数器，这不是用于演示的。
we have this counter and this is this is not for demo
我们要做的是
what we're gonna do is
当你点击计数器的次数过多时
when you click the counter too many times
比方说15次
let's say fifteen times
比方说，15次
let's say 15 times
我们将显示一个警告信息，告诉你，嘿
we're gonna show a warning message that tells you hey
也许是时候考虑做别的事情了
it's maybe time to think about doing something else
也许是时候考虑做一些其他的事情了
然后点击按钮
then clicking the button
然后点击该按钮
所以
so
让我们在这里说，数到15以上的时候
let's go in here and say count more than 15
让我们在这里说，计数超过15个
let's go in here and say counts more than fifteen
我说我说超过15
I said I said more than 15
我说我说超过15 是的，所以
i said i said more than fifteen yeah so
是的，所以
yeah so
警告
warning
你声称这
you claim this
英国这个
uk this
太多次了
too many times
太多次了，该停下来了
too many times time to stop
是时候停下来了
time to stop
如果我回到我的兄弟身边，当然
and if i go back to my brother of course
如果我回到我哥哥身边
and if I go back to my brother
当然，因为计数是15，它的出现
of course because the count is 15 it's appearing
因为数到15它就出现了 但如果我
because the count is fifteen it's appearing but if i
但如果我的新鲜声音还没有出现的话
but if I fresh voice is not appearing yet
新鲜的声音还没有出现
fresh voice is not appearing yet
所以，我点击了一堆倍，是有
so I click a bunch of times and is there
因此，我点击了一堆倍，是有
so i click a bunch of times and is there
现在
now
比方说，我想吃这个警告元素的速率
let's say I want to eat rate on this warning element
让我们说我想在这个警告元素上吃率
let's say i want to eat rate on this warning
元素，我想把它变成红色或类似的东西。
element i want to make it maybe red or something like that well
我想让它变成红色或类似的东西
I want to make it maybe red or something like that
首先，我需要多次点击这个。
well first I need to click this a bunch of times
首先，我需要多次点击这个来显示它
first i need to click this a bunch of times to show it
以显示它，然后我就可以对它进行处理了
to show it and then I can work on it
然后我就可以开始工作了
and then i can work on it
但你可能以前也遇到过这种情况
but you've probably been in the situation before
但你可能已经在之前的情况下
在现实生活中
where in real life
在现实生活中，当你在建设网站时
where in real life when you're building website
当你在建立网站时，你有这些
when you're building website you have these
你有这些
you have these
组件，这些UI元素只出现在像
components these ui elements that only appear in like
组件 这些UI元素
components these UI elements
只有在非常特殊的情况下才会出现
that only appear in like very specific conditions
非常特殊的情况下，比如你是一个管理员或
very specific conditions like when you're an admin or
比如当你是一个管理员或
like when you're an admin or
当你有一个特定的废墟时
when you have a specific ruin
当你有一个特定的废墟时，被设置的数据库
when you have a specific ruin the database that is set
遗憾的是，设置的数据库
the database that is set and unfortunately
和不幸的是
and unfortunately
你的测试数据库没有这个规则
your test database doesn't have that rule
所以你需要模拟它
so you need to mock it
所以你需要以某种方式来模拟它
so you need to mock it somehow
某种程度上，等等
somehow etc
等等
etc
而在这里，我们可以做的是，我们可以把它砍掉。
and and here what we can do is we can just hack it around
在这里，我们可以做的是，我们可以随便黑掉它。
and here what we can do is we can just hack it around
所以我们基本上可以改变这里的主要入口点
so we can basically change the main entry point here
为警告
to be the warning
改为警告组件。
to be the warning component instead
组件来代替
component instead
而这是超级黑客的做法
and this is super hacky
而这是超级黑客的做法，让我们不要
and this is super hacky let's not
我们不会真的这样做，但
we're not gonna actually do this but
我们不会真的这样做，但只是为了向你展示这个想法
we're not gonna actually do this but just to show you the idea
只是为了向你展示
just to show you
这个想法
the idea
让我们来做这个吧
let's let's do that
让我们这样做，让我们把这个导出为组件
let's let's do that so let's export this as components
所以让我们把这个导出为组件
so let's export this as components
然后在这里我们要做警告
and then here we're gonna do warning
然后在这里，我们要做警告
然后回到我的浏览器上
and back to my browser
我看到的是 "无限的"（discomfinite）。
i can see just discomfinite
我可以看到只有discomfinite
I can see just discomfinite
这意味着
which means that
这意味着，现在
which means that now
现在我不需要多次点击计数器了
now I don't need to click the counter a bunch of times
我不需要点击计数器很多次
i don't need to click the counter a bunch of times
来看到它出现
to see it appear
或类似的东西
or anything like that
我也可以把它与我的 "我的 "并排放在一起。
I can also just put that side by side with
我也可以把它和我的ID并排放在一起。
i can also just put that side by side with my
我的ID可以很好地看到它的出现
my id to see it appear nicely
我也可以把它和我的名字放在一起，让它看起来很好。
id to see it appear nicely
你知道，现在我可以进入应用程序的css
and you know now i can go into app that css
而你知道现在我可以进入应用的CSS
and you know now I can go into app that CSS
并让我们说
and let's say
和让我们说
所以这是警告
so this is warning
颜色为红色
color red
红色
酷
cool
现在，这是一个可怕的想法，因为
now this is a terrible idea because
现在，这是一个可怕的想法，因为如果有任何机会，错误地
now this is a terrible idea because if by any chance by mistake
如果通过任何改变
if by any change
错了，你最终会把这个变化并入缅因州
by mistake you end up merging this change into Maine
你最终会把这个改动合并到缅因州的
you end up merging this change into maine
到被部署的主分支中去
into the main branch that gets deployed
那么显然
then obviously
你的用户会有
your users are gonna have
你的用户会有一个完全破碎的体验
your users are gonna have a completely broken experience
一个完全破碎的体验
a completely broken experience
因为他们所看到的
because all they're gonna see
因为他们所看到的是那个组件
because all they're gonna see is that component
是那个组件
is that component
而不是应该看到的应用
as opposed to the app that is supposed to see
相对于应该看到的应用程序，所以
as opposed to the app that is supposed to see so
因此，让我们把这个和
so let's refer this and
让我们把它变成这样，然后
let's refer it this and
让它回到它应该是的样子
get it back to what it's supposed to be
让它回到它应该有的状态
并找到另一个解决方案，所以我打算把这个藏起来
and find another solution instead so i'm gonna hide this
并找到另一个解决方案来代替
and find another solution instead
所以我要把它藏起来
so I'm gonna hide this
我打算停止开发，所以我实际上不需要这个。
I'm going to stop the devs so I don't actually
我打算停止开发，所以我实际上不需要这个了
i'm going to stop the devs so i don't actually need this anymore
不再需要这个
need this anymore
而我将使用特权S
and instead I'm going to use privilege s
取而代之的是我要使用特权S，所以
and instead i'm going to use privilege s so
所以现在我们可以回去添加tsx，我已经有了
so now we can go back to add tsx and I already have
现在我们可以回到添加tsx，而且我已经有了
now we can go back to add tsx and i already have
特权S安装在这里
privilege s installed here
privage s installed here
这对VASCO基地来说是可用的
and this is available for vasco base
而这是可以用于VASCO基地的
也适用于智能网店
also for intelligent web store
也适用于英特尔-简网络商店
also for Intel a Jane web store
现在我可以看到，我有这个
and now i can see that i have this
and now I can see that I have this
链接在每个组件的顶部，所以在特权S中打开应用程序
link on top of each of the components so open app in privilege s
链接在每一个信心的顶部
link on top of each of the confidence
因此，在特权S中打开应用程序
so open app in privilege s
或在这里在特权S中打开警告
or here open warning in privilege s
如果我打开并预先拒绝
if i open up and pre reject
if I open up and pre reject
它要做的就是把它并排打开
what it's going to do is open it side by side
它要做的是在我的ID中并排打开它
what it's going to do is open it side by side within my id
在我的ID内，所以这就像在与代码
within my id so this is like within vs code
所以这就像在VS代码中一样
so this is like within vs code
如果我打开
and if I open
如果我打开警告，它就会向我显示那个自信的
and if i open warning it will show me just that confident
警告，它就会向我显示那个组件
warning it will show me just that component
所以这意味着你可以使用这个
so that means that you can use that
所以这意味着你可以用它来
来测试任何隔离的组件
to test any component in isolation
来测试你想要的任何组件。
to test any component in isolation that you want
你想要的
that you want
而不是必须
as opposed to having to
而不是围绕着不同的
as opposed to having to hack around the
围绕着不同的
hack around the different
不同的入口点或类似的东西
different the entry point or anything like that
入口点或任何类似的东西
the entry point or anything like that
在引擎盖下的特权正在做什么
under the hood what privileges is doing
在引擎盖下
under the hood
特权是什么做的是它的那种模拟
what privileges is doing is it's kind of simulating
是它的那种模拟一个假的入口点
is it's kind of simulating a fake entry point
一个假的进入点
a fake entry point
恰恰是在做黑客攻击你的事
doing precisely the hack that does strude you
恰恰是做了黑客，确实只是给你看
doing precisely the hack that does just show you
但
but
但是，在内存中的方式，不乱用你的文件
but in memory in a way that doesn't mess with your files
在内存中的方式，不乱用你的文件
in memory in a way that doesn't mess with your files
所以现在我可以
so now I can
所以，现在我可以调整这个有点
so now i can tweak this a bit
调整一下
tweak this a bit
可以调整这个
can tweak this
可以稍微调整一下
can tweak this a little
一点点
little bit
一点
bit
你可以看到，它实际上是作为一个类型来更新的
and you can see that it's actually updating as a type
你可以看到它实际上是作为一个类型来更新的
这比起要等到我保存时才更新要好得多。
which is slightly nicer than having to wait until i save
这比要等到我保存
which is slightly
比要等到我保存时才更新要好一些
nicer than having to wait until I save
这是可能的，由于维生素的支持的插件
and this is possible thanks to vit's support for plugins
和这是可能的，由于
and this is possible thanks to
维特对插件的支持
vit's support for plugins
因此，一个特权当然是由维生素提供动力，否则
so a privileges of course is powered by vit otherwise
因此，特权当然是由维生素提供的
so the privileges of course is powered by vit
否则，我不会谈论它在VIDCOFF
otherwise I wouldn't be talking about it at vidcoff
我不会谈论它在vitcoff的
i wouldn't be talking about it at vitcoff
但维生素有这个真正强大的生态系统的插件
but vit has this really powerful ecosystem of plugins
但维生素有这个真正的
but vit has this really
强大的生态系统的插件
powerful ecosystem of plugins
这是在滚筒插件的基础上
which are based on roller plugins
这是以滚筒插件为基础的
而且你可以实现
and you can implement
你可以实现像一个虚拟农场系统
and you can implement like a virtual far system
像一个虚拟文件系统，即使你想
like a virtual file system even if you want to
即使你想
even if you want to
所以在这种情况下
so in this case
所以在这种情况下，其中一个我正在打字
so in this case one of them I'm typing
其中之一，我打字的每一个键程，我正在做的
one of them i'm typing on every key stroke that i'm making
在我做的每一个按键上
on every key stroke that I'm making
它告诉我，这个虚拟文件已经改变了
it's telling that hey this virtual file has changed
它正在处理嘿
it's dealing with hey
这个虚拟文件已经改变了 现在刷新它
this virtual file has changed now refresh it
现在刷新它
now refresh it
这就是这里发生的事情，因为这个维生素是如此之快
and that's what is happening here because this vit is so fast
这就是发生在这里的事情
and that's what is happening here
因为如果它是如此之快，你实际上并没有看到
because if it is so fast you don't actually see
你实际上没有看到任何滞后之间的我打它和
you don't actually see any lag between me typing it and the
任何滞后，我打字和
any lag between me typing it and the
实际发生的变化
actual changes happening
这就是
this is
几乎是
pretty much
幾乎是
譬喻
instance
现在
now
我们现在所看到的组件
the the components that we're looking at right now
the components that we're looking at right now
是超级简单的
are super simple
它们基本上是
they're basically the
UI组件的常量
constants of UI components
UI自信的常量，因为它们不需要任何道具
constants of ui confidence because they don't take any props
因为它们不需要任何道具
because they don't take any props
但是，这个......这个需要这个
but this this takes this
但这个让我们做一些更现实的事情吧
but this let's do something a little bit more realistic
做点更现实的事情
do something a little bit more realistic
让我们说，警告组件实际上
let's say the warning component actually
让我们说，警告组件实际上需要一个信息
let's say the warning component actually takes a message
采取一个信息
takes a message
和一个非点击
and a non click
和一个点击时
and an on click
倾听者
listener
所以我们不点击等于抓取明星点击
so we don't click equals grab star click
所以我们要做的是，点击等同于道具唐纳德点击
so we do on click equals props Donald click
也许我现在应该为gidhabota试点付钱了
maybe i should pay for gidhabota pilot now
也许我现在应该为github的试点付钱了
maybe I should pay for github to pilot now
道具点信息
props dot message
probstad消息
probstad message
好的
okay
顶级脚本编译器的API是在引擎盖下使用的
the top script compiler api is used under the hood
顶级脚本编译器的API是
the top script compiler API is
在引擎盖下使用
used under the hood
以
to
来自动检测
to automatically detect
自动检测组件的道具是什么，所以如果我
automatically detect what are the props of the component so if i
组件的道具是什么？
what are the props of the component
那么，如果我
so if I
点击这个
click on this
点击这个，它就会自动生成
click on this it's going to automatically generate
它将自动生成消息
it's going to automatically generate message
消息，这是一个有效的属性值
message which is a valid value for properties
这是一个有效的属性值
which is a valid value for properties
而且它实际上并不
and it doesn't actually
显示给你看，但在引擎盖下有一个点击监听器正在
show you but under the hood is an on click listener being
显示你
show you
但在引擎盖下是一个点击监听器被生成
but under the hood is an on click listener being
生成，如果我点击这个
generated as well if I click on this
generated as well if i click on this
你可以看到这个弹出函数被打破了
you can see this pop up function proping broke
你可以看到这个弹出式函数被调用了
you can see this pop up function prop invoked
而且每次我点击它的时候
and like every time i click it
和每次我点击它
and every time I click it
让我告诉你
let me show you
稍微高级一些的组件
slightly more advanced components
更高级的组件
来说明一下，这里有这个按钮组件
to to illustrate so here have this button component
来说明
to illustrate
所以这里有这个按钮组件
so here have this button component
它当然也需要子代
and it takes children of course
类型大小和取消点击和
type size and unclick and
类型大小和点击
type size and on click
这里的类型实际上是3个值中的一个，对吗？
and here type is actually one of 3 values right
这里
here
类型实际上是三个值中的一个，对吗？
type is actually one of three values right
要么成功，要么错误，要么透明
either success error or transparent
当我打开这个
when i open this
当我打开这个的时候
when I open this
它就会生成一个非常简单的
it's just going to generate a very very simple
它只是要生成一个非常非常简单的
it's just gonna generate a very very simple
的版本
version of it
我实际上可以生成它的版本
version of it i can actually generate
我实际上可以生成
I can actually generate
道具的随机值，就像这样
random values for the props like this
为道具生成的随机值是这样的
而且我还可以使用其他的完成方式，所以如果我这样做的话
and i can also just use the other completes so if i do
我也可以使用自动完成，所以如果我做了
and I can also just use the auto complete so if I do
类型
type
我实际上有
I actually have
我实际上可以在这些不同的值之间进行选择
i actually have the choice between these different values
在这些不同的值之间进行选择
the choice between these different values
现在，这是免费版本的特权
now this is the free version of privileges
现在，这是免费版本的特权，这是
now this is the free version of privileges which is
这是免费和开放源码的
which is free and open source
免费和开源的
free and open source
也有一个付费的专业版本
there is also a pro version that is paid
而我们的想法是，最好是补贴
and the idea is to ideally subsidize
和想法是理想的补贴
补贴特权项目，这样我就可以花费
the privileges project so that i can spend
资助特权项目，这样我就可以把大部分时间花在
the privileges project so that I can spend
我的大部分时间工作在这上面，而不是
most of my time working on that instead of
做一份正常的工作
working a normal job
让我告诉你这看起来像什么
let me show you what that looks like
让我告诉你这是什么样子的
let me show you what that looks
有一个稍微高级一点的道具编辑器
like there's a slightly more advanced props editor
有一个稍微高级的道具编辑器
there's a slightly more advanced props editor
因此，启用Curl
so enable curl
启用船员
so enable crew
现在，如果我打开按钮
now if i open button
now if I open button
我有
i have
有了这个结构化的编辑器
have this editor which is structured
这个编辑器是结构化的，与之前的编辑器不同
this editor which is structured as opposed to the previous one
而之前的编辑器是基于代码的
as opposed to the previous one which is code based
这是基于代码的
which is code based
我可以更新 我可以像这样添加任何可选的值
and i can update i can add any optional value like this
并且我可以更新
and I can update
我可以像这样添加任何可选的值
I can add any optional value like this
而且我可以选择
and i can choose
and I can choose
在现有的不同价值之间
between the different values that are available
可以在不同的值之间进行选择
顺便说一句，像道具编辑器可以支持任何
and by the way like the props editor can support any
类型的复杂性时
type of type complexity when
类型的复杂性
type of type complexity
你知道嵌套类型数组或所有这类东西吗？
you know nested types arrays or all this kind of stuff
你知道嵌套类型数组或所有这类东西
没有真正有任何问题的
without really having any issues with that
没有任何问题的情况下
所以，如果你想获得强大的用户体验的想法
so if you want the power user experience the ideas
我愿意花钱购买私人的JS专业版
i'd pay for private js pro
我愿意为私人js pro付费
I'd pay for a private js pro
但除此之外，我希望大多数人将
but otherwise i'm hoping that most people will
但除此之外，我希望大多数人都能
but otherwise I'm hoping that most people will
能够过得很好
be able to get get by fine
能够得到告别
be able to get goodbye
只用事先的js就可以了，而不必为它付费
fine with just prior js without having to pay for it
只用私人的js而不用付钱
with just private js without having to pay for it
因此，这将使其失去作用。
so this disable back
所以这就不能再使用了
亲
pro
而现在
and now
现在让我告诉你，它也可以在视图中工作。
and now let me just show you that it does work with view as well
让我告诉你，它确实与视图一起工作
let me just show you that it does work with view
也是如此，我
as well I
我它也能与实体一起工作
i it works with solid as well
它也能和实体一起工作
it works with solid as well
但我们没有时间去做所有的事情，所以
but i we don't have time for everything so
但我没有时间去做所有的事情
but I we don't have time for everything
所以让我们去创建另一个应用程序
so let's go and create another app
让我们去创建另一个应用程序
let's go and create another app
这将是一个视图应用程序
which is gonna be a view app
which is going to be a view app
我的视图应用程序
my view app
这是一个伟大的应用程序名称，我认为没有反应，嘿嘿，坏习惯。
that's a great app name i think no not react hehe bad habits
这是一个伟大的应用程序的名字，我认为
that's a great app name I think
不
no
没有反应的坏习惯
not react bad habits
因此，重新开始我的视图应用程序
so start again my view app
视图标签脚本
view tab script
视图描述
view descript
我将会安装依赖性文件
and i'm gonna install the depenses
我要安装依赖性的东西
and I'm going to install the dependencies
是的
yeah
好的
yep
现在我将打开它
and now I'm gonna open that
现在我要打开它
and now i'm gonna open that
好的
okay
而不是jsx，因为这是一个视图应用程序。
instead of jsx of course because this is a view app
而不是jsx，因为这是一个视图应用程序
我们将有这个视图文件
we're going to have this view files
我们将有这样的视图文件
但它的工作方式是完全一样的
but the way it works is pretty much exactly the same
所以我们在顶部有这个链接
so we have this link at the top
在权限中打开应用程序
open app in privileges
在权限中打开应用程序 我也可以
open app in privileges i can also
我也可以点击这里的按钮来打开
I can also click on that button here to open
点击这里的按钮来打开
click on that button here to open
在特权中打开
opening in privileges
你可以看到，它能够向我展示这个页面
and you can see that it's able to show me the page
你可以看到它能够向我展示这个页面
就像它出现在开发服务器上一样
just like it would appear on the dev server
你可能想知道以前是如何工作的
you might be wondering how does previous work
你可能想知道特权是如何工作的
you might be wondering how does privileges work
所以我之前提到
so I mentioned earlier
所以我提到
so i mentioned
早些时候，它确实与节拍在引擎盖下工作
earlier that it does work with beat under the hood
它确实在引擎盖下与维生素一起工作
that it does work with vit under the hood
它的作用是，它基本上钉住了
and what it does is it basically pins up
一个视频开发服务器动态地
a vid dev server dynamically
一个动态的视频开发服务器
每当你点击打开
whenever you you click on the open
你知道特权中的公司名称，让我进入代码库
you know company name in privileges let me go into the code base
你知道权限中的公司名称
you know company name in privileges
让我进入代码库
let me go into the code base
重要的一点是这个视频管理器
the the important bit is this vid manager
我不打算当然
and i'm not going to of course
当然我也不会
and I am not going to of course
解释这一切是如何工作的
explain how all of this works
但它只是
but it's just
如果你对代码感兴趣，你想知道
if you're interested in the code and you want to you know
如果你对代码感兴趣，并且你想
if you're interested in the code and you want to
你知道认为她周围
you know think her around
认为她的周围，你可以
think her around you can
你可以
you can
你可以进入齿轮项目，并尝试这样做
you can go in on the gear project and and try that
你可以进入github项目，并尝试一下。
you can go in on the github project and and try that
所以
so
这里我们使用的是调用VID创建服务器
here we're using calling vid create server
这里我们使用的是
here we're using
调用 vid dot 创建服务器
calling vid dot create server
而这是
and this is
这不是你可能熟悉的Cli版本
not the cli version of it that you're probably familiar with
不是你可能熟悉的cli
not the cli
的版本，你可能熟悉的是
version of it that you're probably familiar with
这就是
this is
这是节点的API
this is the the node API
节点应用程序接口
the node api
我们在这里动态地创建
where we're dynamically creating
在那里我们动态地创建一个开发服务器
where we're dynamically creating a dev server
一个开发服务器，它基本上是通过一个假的配置
a dev server and it's basically passing a fake configuration
它基本上是通过一个假的配置
and it's basically passing a fake configuration
这是为你的项目自动生成的
that is generated automatically for your project
伴随着一系列的插件，这些插件是
with a bunch of plugins that are
与一堆插件，这些插件
with a bunch of plugins that
有助于特权的正常工作
that are helping privileges to work properly
帮助特权正常工作
are helping privileges to work properly
作为该插件的一部分
as part of this plugins
作为这个插件的一部分
我之前提到的一件事是虚拟文件系统
one thing i mentioned earlier is the virtual file system
我之前提到的一件事是
one thing I mentioned earlier is
虚拟文件系统
the virtual file system
这使我们能够有即时的更新
which enables us to have instant updates
当你在每一个按键上打字时
as you type on every keystroke
当你在每个按键上打字时
这就是这里的虚拟插件
and that's the virtual plugin which is here
和它所做的基本上是每当
and what it does is basically whenever
维特试图从你的磁盘上加载一个犯规
vit is trying to load a foul from your disk
维特试图从你的磁盘上加载一个犯规时
它就会拦截并说
it will kind of intercept that and say
它将拦截它，并说
看，而不是加载appetal tsx的这个内容
look instead of loading this content for appetal tsx
看，而不是为胃口指数加载这些内容
look instead of loading this content for appetite tsx
这里有这个其他的内容
here's this other content
而只是用它来代替，这就是
and just use that instead and that's
而只是用它来代替
and just use that instead
这几乎是它在做的事情
and that's pretty much what it's doing
几乎是它在做什么，所以在
pretty much what it's doing so on on
所以在
so on on
每一次击键，VS好的扩展都会告诉它
every keystroke the vs good extension is telling it
每一次击键，vs好的扩展都会告诉它，嘿
every keystroke the vs good extension is telling it hey
嘿，这个文件已经改变了
hey this file has changed
这个文件已经改变了
this file has changed
然后，虚拟插件会告诉它嘿嘿
and then that the virtual plugin is telling it hey
然后，虚拟插件会告诉它，嘿
我们喜欢这个文件
we love this file
我们喜欢这个文件，而浏览器实际上只是使用了
we love this file and the browser actually just uses the
而浏览器实际上只是使用了
and the browser actually just uses the
esm支持
the esm supports
ESM支持另一个引擎盖，只是重做那一个犯规
the esm supports another hood to just redo that one foul
另一个引擎盖，只是读取它与一个犯规
another hood to just read it with that one foul
并只是做了超级超级快的事项内
and just do that super super quickly within a matter
和只是做，超级超级快
and just do that super super quickly
在许多秒内
within a matter of many seconds
迅速完成。
of many seconds
所以是的
so yeah
我在这里说的是
what i'm saying here
我在这里说的是，preregis将
what I'm saying here is that preregis would
是，如果没有它，preregis根本不可能实现
is that preregis would not be possible at all without it
不可能的
not be possible
没有它就不可能
at all without it
当然，在一个项目中还有一堆其他的东西。
there is a bunch of other stuff of course in a project
还有一堆其他的东西
there is a bunch of other stuff
当然，在这个项目中
of course in the project
其余大部分的魔法都是关于探测的
most of the rest of the magic is about detecting
其余的大部分魔术都是关于检测
代码库中的组件
the components in the code base
代码库中的组件，这些组件实际上是
the components in the code base that's actually
这实际上是
that's actually
视图时相当容易，因为所有
fairly easy when it comes to view because all
视图时相当容易，因为所有的
你所知道的是有一个视图，因此
you know is that there's a view found therefore
你知道的是有一个视图文件
you know is that there is a view file
因此，有一个组件
therefore there is a component
有一个组件
there's a component
但在jsx中，要知道的事情就有点复杂了
but in jsx it's a little bit more complicated to know
但在jsx中，它是一个有点复杂的，知道哦
but in jsx it's a little bit more complicated to know oh
哦，我应该显示这个链接
oh I should be showing this link
我应该显示这个链接 在权限中打开按钮
i should be showing this link open button in privileges
在特权中打开按钮 在这里处置
open button in privileges here at disposition
在这里处置
here at disposition
我确实写了一篇关于这个问题的视频博客文章
I did write a vlog article on that
我确实写了一篇博客文章，我没有
i did write a blog article on that i'm not
我不打算在这里说细节了
I'm not going to go into the details here
但如果你有兴趣的话
going to go into the details here but if you're interested
但如果你有兴趣
but if you're interested
就去fws com
just go to fws com
就去fsws com
just go to fsws com
这就是我的个人网站
that's what my personal website
那是我的个人网站
在那里，你可以阅读更多关于如何工作的确切和再次
where you can read more about how that works exactly and again
在那里你可以阅读更多关于如何工作的确切信息
where you can read more about how that works exactly
再说一遍
and again
这是启用了更好的标签脚本编译器API
this is enabled better tab script compiler API
这是启用的更好的标签脚本编译器API
this is enabled better tab script compiler api
现在，我一直在谈论
now I've been talking about
现在，我一直在谈论的是
now i've been talking about
在特定的组件上工作，有一个很大的
working on specific components and there is a much
在特定的组件上工作，并有一个更
更加知名的
much better known
知名得多的
的工具，叫做storybook
tool to work on individual components called storybook
如果你以前没有见过它，让我来告诉你。
and if you haven't seen it before let me
如果你以前没有见过这个工具，让我
让我告诉你这是什么
let me show you what it is
所以我还有一个叫匈牙利的应用程序，它是
so I have this other app called Hungary which is
所以，我有这个其他的应用程序叫匈牙利，这是
so i have this other app called hungary which is
基本上是一个订购食物的应用程序，我用于演示
just basically a food ordering app that I use for demos
基本上就是一个我用来做演示的订餐软件
just basically a food ordering app that i use for demos
我可以运行年轻的故事书
and i can run the young storybook
and I can run the young storybook
这就是故事书
and so this is storybook
这是在向我展示
this is showing me
例如，这显示了我的按钮的不同版本
this is showing me for example different versions of my button
例如，我的按钮的不同版本
for example different versions of my button
我有一个计数器，里面有不同的值
i have counter with different values in it
I have counter with different values in its
餐馆头等
restaurant header et cetera
餐馆标题等
如果你在使用故事书
if you are using storybook
如果你正在使用故事书，你
if you are using storybook you
你以前可能经历过
you might have experienced before
之前可能经历过缓慢或故事书的问题
might have experienced before the slowness or storybook
缓慢或故事书
the slowness or storybook
基本上你的公司越多
basically the more companies you have
故事书的速度就会变慢
the slower storybook will get
故事书的速度会越来越慢
而Krugis就是来改变这种情况的
and krugis is here to change that
Krugis的出现改变了这一点
如果你想做的事，根本不需要运行故事书。
instead of having to run storybook at all if all you want to do
而不需要运行故事书
instead of having to run storybook at all
如果你想做的是
if all you want to do
只是预览一个特定的故事
is just preview one specific story
就是预览一个特定的故事
你可以直接停止它
you can just stop it
你可以直接停止它，你实际上甚至不需要
you can just stop it you don't actually even
你实际上甚至不需要运行故事书在所有
you don't actually even need to run storybook at all
需要运行故事书
need to run storybook at all
你可以在这里进入你的代码，去看故事
you can go into your code here going to the stories
你可以在这里进入你的代码，进入故事
你可以简单地看到
and you can see simply
它实际上允许你
it actually allows you to
预览你的任何故事，就在那里
preview any of your stories right there
直接在你的ID中
directly in your id
所以你可以看一下默认的证明故事
so you know you can look at the default proof story
所以你知道你可以看一下默认的
so you know you can look at the default
证明故事、成功故事、空中故事等
proof story the success story the air story etc
成功的故事
the success story
空中故事等，你可以
the air story etc and you can
和你可以
and you can
你可以
you can
看到他们的实时更新，以及
see them update live as well
看到他们也在现场更新
就像这样
just like that
这是我认为相当不错的
which is i think pretty cool
这是我认为非常酷的
which is I think pretty cool
你可以
you could
你可以再进一步，实际上如果你想
take it one step further and actually if you wanted to
更进一步，实际上如果你想
只是
just
就能看到你所有的故事书
just see all of your storybook
看到你的所有故事书
see all of your storybook
有
there is
有一个功能，我一直在研究
there is a feature that i've been working on
我一直在研究的一个功能，是尚未
a feature that I've been working on that is not yet
还没有上线，虽然到时候
that is not yet live although by the time
虽然到了股票上市的时候
live although by the time the stock comes
证券来了，也许这将是生活
the stock comes that maybe it will be life
也许它将成为生命
that maybe it will be life
这就是Cli Virgin privilege's，可以让你
which is the cli virgin privilege s that lets you
看到你所有的故事
see all of your stories
我想要的一切，所以让我进入这里
all i want so let me go into here
all I want so let me go into here
我在cli中，所以我要做pnpm开发。
and i'm in the cli so i'm gonna do pnpm dev
and I'm in the cli so I'm gonna do pnpm dev
饥饿
hungry
所以这是开发版本的权限
so this is the dev version of privileges
所以这是特权的开发版本
这可能有一些错误
which probably has a few bugs
是的，因为我运行了错误的命令，开发社区。
yes it does because i ran the wrong command dev community
是的，它是的，因为我
yes it does because I
运行了错误的命令
ran the wrong command
开发社区
dev community
这应该是更好的
that should be better
好了，在这里你可以看到，我
okay so here you can see that i
好的，所以在这里
okay so here
你可以看到，我可以预览任何组件
you can see that I can preview any of the components
可以预览任何组件
can preview any of the components
就像这样，这里有一个初始
just like that there is an initial
就像这样
just like that
有一个最初的加载时间，但之后是
there is an initial load time but after that is
但之后的加载时间就相当快了
load time but after that is pretty fast
相当快
pretty fast
是的
yeah
当然，如果你更新文件
and of course if you update the file
你知道它将在这里即时更新
you know it will update here instantly
我不仅可以显示这些故事
i can also not only show the stories
我也可以不只显示故事
I can also not only show the stories
但如果我点击显示组件
but if i click show components
但如果我点击显示组件，我可以显示
but if I click show components I can show
我可以显示
i can show
我可以单独显示任何组件
any component individually
所以这里有一个按钮，我们之前已经看到了
so here have the button that we've seen earlier
在这里我有
where i have
在这里我可以
where I have I can
我可以改变大小，并以我想要的方式预览它
i can change the size and just preview it however i want
改变大小，并以我想要的方式进行预览
change the size and just preview it however I want
下一件事
the next thing
下一件事，我即将建立
the next thing I'm about to build
我正准备建造
i'm about to build
这可能只在专业版中出现。
this is probably going to be only in the pro version
这可能只在专业版中出现，但
this is probably gonna be only in the pro version but
但你将会有保存的功能
but you're going to have the save
你将会有这个
you're gonna have this
保存按钮，让你创建一个新的故事
save button that lets you create a new story
按钮，让你创建一个新的故事
button that lets you create a new story
或者如果你正在查看一个特定的故事
or if you're viewing a specific story
或者如果你正在浏览一个特定的故事
你就可以将道具连接起来
you can twig the props
你可以将道具连接起来，然后点击保存并添加到故事中。
you can twig the props and just hit save and add that story so
然后点击保存并添加该故事
and there's just hit save and add that story
因此，这个想法是，你不需要
so the idea being that you don't need to
这个想法是，你不需要
the idea being that you don't need to
真正处理的故事文件，将手动了
really deal with stories files that will manually anymore
真正处理的故事文件，
really deal with stories files that
愿意手动处理
will manually anymore
所有你做的是你使用权限来创建
all you do is you use privileges to create
所有你做的是你使用权限来创建他们和管理他们
all you do is you use privileges to create them and manage them
编写和管理它们
them and manage them
而且你再也不用处理这些代码了
and you just never deal with that code ever again
我认为这应该让你有更多的机会
which i think should make you quite a bit
我认为这应该使你
which I think should make you
相当多的生产力
quite a bit more productive
如果你要处理大量的故事书，就会更有成效。
more productive if you're dealing with a lot of with storybook
如果你要处理大量的
if you're dealing with a lot of
故事书
with storybook
这是即将到来的，希望在今年年底之前
that's upcoming hopefully before the end of the year
这是即将到来的
that's upcoming
希望在今年年底之前
hopefully before the end of the year
但我有一个8个月大的孩子要照顾，所以
but i do have an eight month old baby to take care of so
但我确实有一个8个月大的婴儿需要照顾，所以
but I do have an 8 month old baby to take care of so
时间表是困难的
timelines are difficult
时间表是很难坚持的
timelines are difficult to stick to
坚守
to stick to
这就是关于特权的问题，所以我
that's about it about privileges so i
这就是关于特权的问题
that's about it about privileges
所以我
so I
我很想邀请你去看看特权网
would love to invite you to check out privileges com
尝试一下，了解更多信息
to try it out and learn a bit more
这里有很多你可能需要的配置
there's quite a bit of configs that you might need
有很多你可能需要的配置
所以我给你看的所有的例子都是
so all of the examples that i've shown you are
so all of the examples that I've shown you are
绝对零配置
absolutely zero config
absolutely 0 config
但这是相当
but it's quite
但很有可能，如果你有一个更多的
but it's quite likely that if you have a more
有可能，如果你有一个更复杂的项目，如它的下一个
likely that if you have a more complex project like it's next
复杂的项目
complex project
像它小于
like it's less than
你正在使用氧化还原或类似的东西
you're using redox or something like that
你在使用氧化还原或类似的东西
你将需要设置
you will need to set up
你将需要设置像说唱者一样的东西来设置
you will need to set up like rappers to set up the
饶舌的人，以建立你知道的反应背景或
rappers to set up the you know react context or
反应上下文或
react context or
设置别名的所有这些东西，所以
set up aliases all these kind of stuff so
设置别名，所有这些东西
set up aliases all these kind of stuff
所以所有这些都在网站上有记录
so all of that is documented on the website
所有这些在网站上都有记录
all of that is documented on the website
就是这样，谢谢你的聆听。
that's about it thank you so much for listening and
这就是它
that's about it
非常感谢您的收听和
thank you so much for listening and
享受会议的其余部分
enjoy the rest of the conference
再见
see ya